M. AGHITS SEPTIAN ALFARIZI

WEB DEVELOPER

Purwakarta, Indonesia | Phone : +6281210166462 | Email : muhammadaghits15@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammadaghits/ | Website: https://muhammadaghits.github.io

ABOUT ME

I am a technology information (IT) professional with a specialized skillset in web development. I possess in-depth knowledge and practical experience in web programming languages. With a strong background in web development, I have the ability to design, develop, and optimize efficient and intuitive web applications. I also possess skills in integrating various web technologies and solving complex technical problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer (2022 - present)

- Designed and developed a web application for promote and sales UMKM products using Laravel,
 Tailwind CSS and MySQL.
- Designed and developed a web application for manage regional student organization administrator data using Laravel, Bootstrap dan MySQL.
- Designed and developed a web application for point of sale system using Laravel, Bootstrap and MySQL.

Web Developer (August, 2021 - October, 2021) - Internship SMA Kartika XIX-1, Bandung

 Designed and developed a web application for management of incoming and outgoing mail archives using Codelgniter, Bootstrap and MySQL.

SKILLS

Soft Skills

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Javascript, Vue.js, React.js, PHP, Codeigniter, Laravel, MySQL, Oracle, Git & RESTful API.

Hard Skills

Teamwork, problem sloving, adaptable, communicative, critical thinking & time management.

CERTIFICATION

Junior Web Developer (2022)

PT. Telkom Prima Cipta Certifia - BNSP Link : https://drive.google.com/file/d/1H8y_9Be dBJ0-5Cb9SCc982W8zddYJ5tl/view?usp=drive.google.com/file/d/1H8y_9Be e link Database Programming With SQL (2022)

Oracle Academy - Oracle

Link: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1wiTs2x 6fl6ts8iDC65GuS3SeptW5d8wG/view?usp= drive link

EDUCATION

Universitas Komputer Indonesia (2018 - 2022)

S1 - Informatics Engineering | GPA: 3,32

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

HMIF UNIKOM (2020 - 2021)

PWTI Division - Committee